32vegas.com 2018-02-22

# 32Red Online Casino's Privacy Policy - 32Red Online Casino

A bit of privacy is always good – especially when we’re getting dressed in the morning or singing in the shower. For your protection, 32Red has pulled together this handy privacy policy so you can know how we collect and store your information.

First of all you should know that this website (the 'Site') is operated by and information collected from this Site is collected by 32Red Ltd, a British company incorporated and based in Gibraltar (company registration no. 83626) ('32Red', 'us' or 'we').

32Red respects the privacy of its online visitors and users of the Site. 32Red recognises the importance of protecting certain information collected from users and has adopted this Privacy Policy to explain how 32Red gathers, stores, and uses information provided by users through the Sites as described below.

## Acceptance of Privacy Policy...

If you use the Site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and 32Red will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site, after we either personally notify you or generally post changes on the Site, will constitute your acceptance of those changes.

## Our cookie policy and use of information stored on your device...

A cookie is a text file containing information about you and your device which is stored on your computer to provide information needed by the user on a regular basis. Cookies are often used to save website customisations and website login information so that the website knows who you are. Cookies can also be used to tailor the experience that you get from a particular website, and provide you with personalised offers as well as give important information as to how the website is performing. Here at 32Red we use cookies for the following purposes:

  * To provide a full customer experience within the casino.
  * To recognise you as an existing customer and to allow you to login to your account more easily.
  * To collect vital information on the running of our website, this allows us to improve our service to you.
  * To understand how you are using our website, to help us improve our service.
  * To make our marketing activity relevant to you - this helps us to ensure we show you the most relevant offers both on our own site and on others.

We may also work with external advertising networks who use 3rd party cookies to collect information on your preferences, meaning we can show adverts and offers that are tailored to you. For more information of cookies please visit <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/>

An IP address is a number that uniquely identifies your computer on the internet. 32Red Online Casino may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, security, troubleshooting, and compiling aggregate information (such as how many visitors logged on to the Site). When you visit a particular web page on the Site, our servers may log your IP address. We may also use your IP address to ensure that we give you the best customer experience, and provide you with a service in your local currency, where applicable.

## Public Messages...

Any information that is disclosed in a public area of the Site by users is public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information on the Site. If you voluntarily disclose information in a public area of the Site, such as a message board, that information may be collected and used by a third-party to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements or for other purposes. We do not control the actions of these third parties in public areas of the Site, so if you disclose information in a public area, you do so at your own risk

## Choice/Opt-out...

32Red may use customer contact information provided by you to send information about 32Red Online Casino and the products, Services and/or Sites for which you subscribed or otherwise used or accessed, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials.

32Red Online Casino provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from 32Red when you are asked to provide information to us. In addition, 32Red gives users the option of discontinuing receipt of general communications from 32Red, although users may still receive important messages (as defined below under 'Collection and Use of Information'). To unsubscribe from 32Red’s marketing emails, click on the unsubscribe link in the footer of the message or contact our Player Experience Team.

## International Transfer, Storage and Security of Information...

The personal information you provide to us may be stored and processed outside the United Kingdom in any country in which 32Red Online Casino or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 32Red will take reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure.

## Collection and Use of Information...

We may require your personal information for access to certain parts of the Site and related products or Services. We may collect your personal information when you: (a) register to become a member or user of our Services; (b) voluntarily provide it when you use the Site; (c) disclose it in a public area of the Site; or (d) provide it when you communicate with us. If you register to become a member or user of our Services through the Site, we may use the personal information that you provide for billing purposes, and to administer and manage your account and provide promotional updates regarding such products or Services as contemplated above.

32Red Online Casino may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical, Service, important account balance information (including the increase of your cash account balance on a no purchase necessary basis) or security issues related to a product or Service you requested, confirming you requested a product or Service, or providing periodic updates or information relating to the product or Service you requested. For so long as you are subscribed to a Service, you will not be able to choose to unsubscribe from these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the Service you have chosen.

32Red Online Casino may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited Services on our behalf, including without limitation, identity verification, payment processing and the provision of software. 32Red Online Casino will only provide these companies that information which is reasonably required to perform the Service, and they will be prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

We will validate name, address and other personal information supplied by you against appropriate third party databases. By accepting these terms and conditions you consent to such checks being made. In performing these checks personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Credit Reference Agency which may keep a record of that information. You can rest assured that this is done only to confirm your identity, that a credit check is not performed and that your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated securely and strictly in accordance with the Data Protection legislation.

In order to assist us in processing your transaction where your credit card may have been declined, we receive further information from your bank about the reasons for this. We use this information to facilitate completion of your transaction so that we can provide our service to you. We do not use this information for any other purposes.

Generally, when our third-party contractors or partners collect and/or have access to your personal information we require that they adhere to our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of your personal information.

32Red Online Casino may elect to share your personal information with qualified third-party partners for marketing or other similar purposes but only where you agree to share such information. Such partners will be prohibited from disclosing or using such information except for the limited purposes which the users have consented to.

The Site contains links to third-party websites. When you follow these links you leave the Site and are transferred to a third party website. You should be aware that these third-party websites may have their own information collection practices and privacy policies. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties that have websites linked to the Site. If you follow a third-party advertisement or link, the privacy policies of the third-party website that you link to will govern the use of your information by that website's operator. The Privacy Policy does not extend to these external websites and companies. Please refer directly to the privacy policies on such third party websites. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise. Accordingly, please make sure you are aware of and comfortable with the privacy policies of any third-party websites to which you are transferred by following a link.

32Red may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process or any governmental request; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of 32Red or its affiliated companies; (c) enforce the Terms and Conditions; or (d) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of 32Red' employees, users of the Site, or members of the public.

In the event of a merger or consolidation of 32Red, or the sale of all or substantially all of its stock or assets, or the transfer of the operation and distribution of certain products or Services to a third-party, or bankruptcy of 32Red, your personal information may be transferred to 32Red' successor or assign resulting from such events.

We may also disclose your personal information to a third-party that alleges that you have infringed their intellectual property rights, subject to reasonable verification of such claims.

By using the Site, users agree that 32Red may share with other parties aggregate information and non-identifiable information gathered by 32Red in the course of the continuing use of the Site. Aggregate information or non-identifiable information may be used to improve the Site, for internal marketing studies, or simply to collect demographic information about users.

## No Absolute Safeguards...

Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorised third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control.

## Your Role in Protecting Your Privacy...

Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any account ID or password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online.

Corrections, Updates and Removal of Information If you are concerned with the accuracy of the personal information provided by you and maintained by 32Red or would like your personal information removed from 32Red' records, you may use the tools made available on the Site to update or remove such information. 32Red reserves the right to charge a reasonable fee for supplying copies of such information. If you choose to delete your personal information, you may not be able to access some areas of the Site and/or Services to which you have subscribed. We will not provide a refund for any prepaid Service which is inaccessible to you because of the deletion of your personal information. We may, however, still retain your personal information in our files to resolve disputes, to enforce our user agreement, and to comply with any and all technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Site.

Last updated 26th April 2017

32Red Ltd is licensed by the Government of Gibraltar (Licence No.019) and regulated by the Gibraltar Gambling Commissioner.

Our services in the UK are licensed and regulated by the UK Gambling Commission (Licence No: 000-039430-R-319293-004) 32Red Ltd., 741 Europort, Gibraltar
